<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collaborators on Resonate</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Collaborators on Resonate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Harris</title>
      <link>/team/peterharris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/peterharris/</guid>
      <description>Active as a web developer since the 90s, Peter has built hundreds of sites across dozens of industries. He has focused especially on the music industry, collaborating with numerous musicians, from struggling artists to mid-level bands (and even a few platinum-selling superstars). Working by day as a web dev, Peter had a night hobby as a DJ and electronica producer. This led to experiments with virtually every web and music publishing platform available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignacio Baigorria</title>
      <link>/team/ignaciobaigorra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ignaciobaigorra/</guid>
      <description>Nacho has more than 10 years of experience as a consultant for Accenture. During his career he has worked in multiple industries but always with one common goal: to help answer complex business questions. He joined Resonate to build new paths in the music industry for independent artists. He is passionate about numbers, achieving collective goals and music. As a percussionist he has developed a special interest on afro-uruguayan &amp;ldquo;candombe&amp;rdquo;. Based in Buenos Aires, Argentina, he lives with Denise and Vera, their daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marie Gauthier</title>
      <link>/team/mariegauthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/mariegauthier/</guid>
      <description>Marie found out about Resonate during the Music Tech Fest taking place at Berlin&amp;rsquo;s Funkhaus in May 2016, where the co-op took part in the #MTFLabs: Blockchain event. As a creative web developer, music lover and maker, she believes in the better economic and social model for music streaming that Resonate enables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire Tolan</title>
      <link>/team/clairetolan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/clairetolan/</guid>
      <description>Trained as a writer and archivist, Claire Tolan learned to program somewhere between the Yosemite National Park archives, the University of Michigan School of Information, and the Tactical Technology Collective in Berlin. She has built websites and software for NGOs, universities and start-ups, and has been a decentralization advocate since registering her first diaspora* account in 2012, which (weirdly) provided her with the opportunity to move to Berlin. Since 2014, she has hosted &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re Worth It,&amp;rdquo; the ASMR show on Berlin Community Radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Augustin Godiscal</title>
      <link>/team/augustingodiscal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/augustingodiscal/</guid>
      <description>Augustin is a developer from Belgium. With a background in computer graphics, he now works largely as a creative software developer. His work has always been multifaceted, and he enjoys doing many different things, from design to code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Keenan</title>
      <link>/team/mattkeenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/mattkeenan/</guid>
      <description>Matt has been writing code since the tender age of 11, and first ventured onto the Internet (ARPANET back then) in &amp;lsquo;77. He has worked in start ups for more than 20 years with roles from lead developer to CTO. He has done DevOps and systems networking, and has even been known to occasionally do technology lobbying. In his younger days, Matt participated in various choirs, and also studied the piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wilson Fanestil</title>
      <link>/team/wilsonfanestil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/wilsonfanestil/</guid>
      <description>Wilson is an inter-media artist and designer, improvising in experimental production environments. He uses video, 3D graphics and live data streams to create generative, experiential artworks. Wilson is committed to clarity, minimalism and textural density in all his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Dubuis</title>
      <link>/team/lukedubuis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/lukedubuis/</guid>
      <description>As the owner of an independent record label, Luke is very aware of the ways in which the music industry fails artists. He’s also a long-term NTS radio DJ, and strongly values community, independence and culture. Luke originally comes from London, but recently relocated to Berlin to work for Resonate as Head of Marketing. He’s highly driven to help build an equitable platform that all independent artists can share in and benefit from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mollie Zhang</title>
      <link>/team/molliezhang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/molliezhang/</guid>
      <description>Mollie Zhang is a writer, artist and musician, currently based in Berlin. As a freelance writer and editor, their work has appeared in publications including The Quietus and CTM Festival Magazine. As a DJ, they’ve recorded mixes for NTS and Berlin Community Radio.
Mollie is a fan of a wide range of sounds (but has a particular weakness for breakbeat). Though they’re a social media-phobe, you can find them lurking online at zzhhaa@protonmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Hatch</title>
      <link>/team/jimhatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jimhatch/</guid>
      <description>Jim Hatch is an artist manager, producer, creative director and event producer. While studying at Leeds College of Music, Jim set up and ran an arts and music promotional company, which produced events for the Lumen Art Prize, Leeds Digital, and Live at Leeds, among others. Jim has spent time producing and touring with his own band, and also founded his own management company, through which he is currently working to foster the careers of several young artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nora Germain</title>
      <link>/team/noragermain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/noragermain/</guid>
      <description>Nora Germain is a musician and author based in Los Angeles. As a violinist she has appeared on over 100 recordings, and has collaborated with Sam Smith, Jon Batiste and Stay Human, Postmodern Jukebox, Tommy Emmanuel, Jeff Goldblum, JMSN, The Eckhart Tolle Foundation, Jacob Collier, Musical Director for Prince Morris Hayes, Glenn Frey of the Eagles, Louis Cole of KNOWER, Glee, Drunk History, Disney Vacations and many others.
She is also a singer and songwriter, has released seven of her own albums, and in 2016 she published her first inspirational book, &amp;ldquo;Go For It &amp;hellip;Surviving the Challenges of Becoming an Artist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Crane</title>
      <link>/team/alexcrane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/alexcrane/</guid>
      <description>Alex has worked as a designer, developer, musician and audio engineer. He grew up playing and watching live music in an underground hardcore, metal, punk, and noise rock scene in Tucson, Arizona in the 90s. Later he worked as a recording engineer in the San Francisco Bay Area, where he experienced a struggling music industry firsthand.
The need to survive and an interest in visual arts led Alex to learn graphic design as a trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avi Ashkenazi</title>
      <link>/team/aviashkenazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aviashkenazi/</guid>
      <description>Avi is a designer and technologist, who’s worked on consumer, enterprise and retail products. Avi founded 2PAx, a restaurant optimization system that fosters efficiency. As part of the Samsung Innovation Lab, Avi created UX concepts that are now implemented and patented through Samsung products.
Now, Avi helps startups design and develop products successfully. He has worked with more than 20 companies, including Google, Sam Labs, Deutsche Telekom and Google. Previously, Avi was one of the creators of MusicTechFest, giving musicians, industry leaders and hackers the chance to connect and create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aleksandar Nikov</title>
      <link>/team/aleksandarnikov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aleksandarnikov/</guid>
      <description>Aleksandar is a guy that wears glasses (but not necessarily geeky ones). He&amp;rsquo;s a classical philologist with lots of printing ink on his hands, as well as a promising amateur photographer without a single printed photograph. Aleks is the proud owner of a CHAO 700, the first modular DIY synth in his neighborhood. He&amp;rsquo;s a returning tourist and weekend adventurer in the sphere of electronic music – Master Clock, Knight of the Kick Drum and Knight of the Hi-hats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darryl Neudorf</title>
      <link>/team/darrylneudorf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/darrylneudorf/</guid>
      <description>Darryl Neudorf has spent the last 35 years in the music industry. Starting off as musician, composer and performer for the Canadian post-punk band 54&amp;frasl;40, he then branched out to engineering, producing, and mixing. Recordings that Darryl has been a part of have reached Gold and Platinum status in Canada and the US, top ten on Billboard, earned Grammy nominations and a Juno award, and a Juno nomination for Engineer of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>